luvemorleavem.com 2008-12-17

# Relationship Advice for Women - LuvemOrLeavem.com

**Registration**

In order to use or post your content on this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give us contact information (such as your name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. You are also required to provide information such as your date of birth, country, zip code and gender to us. We use such information to offer products and services that may be of interest to you, to facilitate your use of the site, and to provide you a more personalized experience on our site. Luvemorleavem.com, LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on this Web site. 

**Tell-A-Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [[Administrator@luvemorleavem.com](mailto:administrator@luvemorleavem.com)] to request that we remove this information from our database.

**Special Offers and Updates**

We will occasionally send you newsletters, information on special promotions, or your account updates. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications by opting out of these communications at your registration phase or through your account page. 

**Service-related Announcements**

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

**Customer Service**

We will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email.

**Profile**

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs and other means to create a “profile” of your preferences in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. We may share your profile with other third parties, but in aggregate form only.

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**

We occasionally share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

**Personally identifiable information**

We do not share personally identifiable information with third parties without your express consent, except as expressly set forth in other parts of this privacy policy.

**Service Providers**

We may use third parties to provide certain services on our site. We will only share your personally identifiable information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information.

If you no longer wish to receive our promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by emailing us at [Administrator@Luvemorleavem.com]. We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our [MEMBER ACCOUNT PAGES], or you may contact us at [[Administrator@Luvemorleavem.com](mailto:administrator@luvemorleavem.com)] or [Luvemorleavem.com LLC, P.O. Box 1296, Mount Juliet, TN 37121] to opt-out.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We may link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. We may also use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies or log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s "help" file. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See "Third Party Advertisers."

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**

We or our third party advertising or web analytics partners may employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We may tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see "Choice and Opt-out."

**Third Party Advertisers**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by our advertising partner. We may share Web site usage information about users with a reputable third party for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site.

Our third party advertising partner may use cookies and clear GIFs on this site, which allow it to recognize a user's cookie when a user visits this site. The information that our third party advertising partner collects and shares through this technology is not personally identifiable.

**Links to Other Sites**

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Luvemorleavem.com. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at Administrator@Luvemorleavem.com or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below.

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [[Administrator@Luvemorleavem.com](mailto:administrator@luvemorleavem.com)]

In the event Luvemorleavem.com, LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. We will notify you via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. If you continue to use this site after we have made a change to this policy, you have agreed to the revised policy, and the revised policy will apply with respect to all of your personally-identifiable information, even if it was collected before the revised policy was instituted.

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [Administrator@Luvemorleavem.com](mailto:administrator@luvemorleavem.com), or Luvemorleavem.com LLC, P.O. Box 1296, Mount Juliet, TN 37121.
